JENNY WONG

PROFILE

UC Davis graduate with a background in Design and Computer Science. Experienced with user-focused design and converting designs into functional applications/websites. Engages in mindful and compassion driven approach to understand, connect with, and meet client needs.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UX/UI Design Intern, July 2024-Present *Meetomate*

- Refined and updated Meetomate logo and UI designs for MVP versions
- Analyzed usability testing, organizing feedback to guide design iterations
- Collaborated on updating visual style guides, ensuring consistency across logos, colors, text fields, and user flows
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to enhance product design

Educational Assistant, Aug 2023–Jun 2024 *ProCare Therapy*

- Practiced mindfulness and compassion driven approach to build trusting relationships with special needs students
- Coordinated and tailored lesson plans based on individual students' learning abilities

Programming Instructor, Jun 2022-Sep 2023 Coding Minds Academy

- Hosted multiple different programming classes: Python, Flutter, JavaScript, Scratch, one-on-one or in small groups
- Fostered critical thinking and problem-solving skills by encouraging students to explore and discover solutions independently through guidance and prompted questioning
- Improved HTML, CSS, and JavaScript curriculums by revising outdated content and creating engaging topic-focused, guided projects
- Crafted a visually cohesive exercise website in collaboration with developers, seamlessly reflecting the academy's visual identity

Front-End Development Tutor, Jun-Jul 2021 & Sep-Dec 2021 University of California, Davis

- Hosted weekly tutoring sessions to assist students with assignment and project specific questions
- Empowered individuals to grasp HTML and CSS concepts by offering guidance on design and development decisions for their websites
- Delivered constructive feedback to streamline and optimize their code structure



(510) 520-7124



jennywong270@gmail.com



Bay Area, CA

SKILLS

- Detail-Oriented
- Organized
- Responsible

Technical skills

- *Design*: Figma, Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, XD, InDesign, Acrobat
- Programming: HTML, CSS, lavascript
- Tools: Git, Github, FlutterFlow

UX Methods

- User Interviews, Surveys
- User Flows, Personas, Journey Maps
- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- Usability Testing
- Design Lifecycle
- Design System

EDUCATION

University of California, Davis -

lune 2022 | 3 647

- Major: Bachelor of Arts, Design
- Minor: Bachelor of Science
 Computer Science

SOCIALS

linkedin.com/in/jennywong00 github.com/jyw270 jyw270.github.io/portfolio

REFERENCES

Available upon request